A Guide to the Papers of James Taylor Ellyson, 1865, 1896-1910
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Jones, R.M. (1910 Feb 15)
Jones, Sam D. (1900 Jun 28)
Jones, Walter C. (1900 Jul 18)
Jones, Wilie (1908 Jul 20, Jul 21)
Jones, William Atkinson (1905 Mar 7, Mar 13; 1909 Jun 28)
Jones, William H. (1900 Jul 11)
Jordan, H. (1900 Jun 15; 1909 Nov 3)
Jordan, J.R. (1905 Apr 29; 1910 Sept 6)
Jordan, O.E. (1897 Oct 25)
Jordan, Olive H. (1909 Nov 3)
Jordan, R.L. (1908 Jun 1)
Jordan, Robert O. (1899 Jul 28)
Joyner, G.G. (1910 Oct 8)
Kane, Robert R. (1899 Nov 11)
Kay J.J. (1905 Jun 30)
Kean, W. (1896 Nov 21; Dec 16)
Keaton, L.M. (1905 Jul 7)
Keel, H.T. (1905 Jun 17)
Kegley, Fulton (1905 May 4)
Keigwin, H.A. (1909 Jun 2)
Kenan, John [ ] (1909 Oct 9)
Kenan, Thomas Stephen (1908 Dec 31; 1909 Aug 8)
Kendrick, J.B. (1909 Sept 9)
Kendrick, W.J. (1900 Jul 5)
Kennard, John Hanson (1907 Jun 7)
Kennedy, S.M. (1905 Mar 23)
Kent, Charles William (1909 Sept 11, Oct 22; 1910 Jan 14)
Kent, Samuel D. (1909 Aug 11)
Kerfoot, F.W. (1899 Sept 11)
Kern, John W. (1906 May 15)
Kerr, John W. (1908 Aug 24)
Kilby, Wilbur J. (1900 Mar 30)
Kimball, John H. & Company (1900 Jan 10)
Kincheloe, John W. (1899 Sept 4; 1909 Jul 26; n.y. Apr 12)
King, Alexander (1899 Oct 30)
King, G.N.P. (1900 Mar 12)
Kirby, Mrs. E.T. (1909 Jun 21)
Kohlsaat, Charles W. (1906 Dec 27; 1907 Jan 2, Mar 9, Mar 20)
Koiner, G.W. (1899 Nov 4; 1909 Jan 11)
Krause, Mrs. William (1908 Oct 14)
Kusell, George B. (1896 Dec 16; 1899 Oct 30)
Lake, Felix (1907 Oct 12)
Lamb, Edwin T. (1908 Dec 9)
Lamb, John (1899 Sept 23, Dec 28; 1900 Jan 5, May 15, Jul 28)
1905 Mar 7, Apr 11, Apr 28, May 1 (1908 Jan 14; 1909 Jan 6, Apr 6, Aug 11; 1910 Jun 16)
Land, W.A. (1908 Aug 28; 1909 Nov 27)
Landrum, W.W. (1900 Jan 30, Jul 28)
Lane, G.E.T. (1909 Feb 22, Mar 25)
L'Anser, (1899 Dec 1)
LaRue, J. (1909 Sept 20)
Lassiter, Charles T. (1909 Nov 12)
Lassiter, Francis Rives (1900 Mar 5)
Lauck, J.S. (1909 Mar 18)
Laughton, John E. Jr. (1905 Mar 7)
Lavender, P.E. (1905 Jul 15)
Lawless, Joseph T. (1909 Jul 6)
Lawrence, Chester B. Jr. (1900 Jan 2)
Lawrence, Frank D. (1909 Feb 10;1910 Feb 14)
Lawson, D.M. (1909 Feb 15)
Lea, W.B. (1900 Jan 15)
Leake, William J. (1906 Nov 3, Nov 6)
Learned, M.D. (1906 Jan 6)
Lee, Miss Augusta (1909 Sept 30)
Lee, Charles N. (1905 Jul 13)
Lee, Mrs. James O. (1909 Jun 15)
Lee, R.B. (1900 Jul 2, Jul 5)
Lee, R.E. Jr. (1906 Mar 29)
Lee, R.H. (1905 Jul 8)
Lee, William McDonald (1899 Oct 25; 1909 Jun 15, Jul 9, Aug 3)
Leeton, Heth (1900 Jun 7)
Leslie, J.A. (1909 Jun 17, Aug 2)
Lesner, John Adam (1907 Oct 12; 1909 Jun 14, Aug 11; 1910 Apr 11, Aug 27)
Lester, John A. (1905 Jul 12)
Letcher, Greenlee Davidson (1899 Dec 30; 1900 Jan 5, May 11)
Lewis, William Travers (1910 Sept 8)
Lincoln, A.T. (1909 Nov 3)
Lindsey, J.F. (1909 Nov 25)
Lion, Thomas H. (1907 Oct 16)
Lippincott, J.B. Company (1909 Sept 9)
Little, Adrian (1899 Dec 24)
Littrell, A.W. (1909 Apr 7)
Lloyd, Joseph W. (1909 Jun 10)
Lofton, Lucien (1909 Aug 7)
Long, Armistead R. (1909 Jul 2)
Long, William G. (1910 Mar 25)
Lookabill, L.E. (1905 Jul 1)
Lora (1908 Aug 22)
Lord, Eliot (1900 Jan 26, Mar 7)
Lord and Hewlett Architects (1910 Jan 11)
Lorimer, George C. (1899 Jul 20, Dec 14)
Louderback, D.S. (1907 Oct 12)
Louthan, F. Garrett (1910 Feb 8)
Louthan, Henry Thompson (1899 Nov 21, Nov 24; 1900 Jun 15)
Love, J.W. (1905 Jul 15)
Loving, John T. (1908 Aug 12, Aug 24)
Luckett, D.G. (1900 Jun 11)
Ludington, Arthur (1909 Oct 7)
Lundy, E.L. (1899 Oct 27)
Lyle, Edward (1900 Apr 13)
Lynch, T.A. (1900 May 9; 1905 Apr 29; 1906 Oct 20)
Lyon, Frank S. (1909 Aug 9)
Lyon, J.V. (1905 Jul 7)
McAllister, Joseph Thompson (1900 Jul 3)
McCabe, J.B. (1897 Oct 17; 1905 Apr 29)
McCabe William Gordon (1909 Jan 18)
McCaul, Thomas V. (1899 Jun 15, Nov 28; 1900 Jun 20, Jul 14; 1909 Jul 6, Jul 16)
McClaugherty, W. Walter (1900 Jul 6, Jul 14)
McClintic, E.H. (1905 Jun 28)
McCormick, Marshall (1896 Nov 20)
McCue, William T. (1897 Oct 26; 1900 Mar 26)
McCullough, N.H. (1900 Jan 7)
McCurdy, H.A. (1900 Feb 10)
McGavock, J.W. (1910 Mar 16)
Macgill, James (1900 Jan 30)
McGilvray, J.A. (1905 Apr 8)
McGlone, J.V. (1907 Nov 20; 1909 Feb 23, Apr 9, Apr 23, Aug 11, Sept 6)
MacGregor, Malcolm (1900 June 18)
Mchaughan J.A. (1909 Jun 16)
McHugh, Charles A. (1909 Dec 23)
McIlwaine, Richard (1899 Jul 28; 1902 Oct 14)
McIntyre, R.A. (1910 Sept 21)
McIntosh, David G. (1909 Oct 18, Oct 19)
Mack, Norman E. (1909 Jan 21, Jun 15)
McKean, William Shields (1908 May 14; 1909 Sept 1, Sept 16; 1910 Aug 13)
Mackey, Crandal (1910 Feb 12)
McLaurin, M. (1910 Jan 21)
McLean, F.W. (1910 Sept 12)
MacLean, Samuel R.(1909 Nov 15; 1910 Jan 28; Mar 7)
MacMackin, B. (1906 Sept 19)
McMahon, John J. (1910 Jul 26)
McManaway J.M. (1909 Mar 11)
Madison, E.C. (1900 Jul 27)
Mahood, William A. (1897 Oct 20)
Mann and Brown Florists (1909 Jan 19)
Mann, G.C. (1909 Feb 8)
Mann, James (1909 Nov 22)
Mann, William Hodges (1899 Oct 18, Oct 26;1900 Mar 9; 1909 Aug 27, Nov 4, Nov 22; 1910 Apr 14)
Mapie, Eugene C. (1900 Jan 12)
Mapie, N.H. (1897 Oct 27, Nov 4)
Marbury, Leonard (1896 Dec 3)
Marquis, A.N. and Company (1909 Nov 4)
Marshall, John A. (1910 Jan 4)
Marshall, Mrs. M.W. (1908 Jan 16)
Marshall, R.J. (1909 Jul 9)
Martin, Alvah H. (1908 Oct 10; 1909 Jan 29)
Martin, John I (1909 May 17, Dec 23)
Martin, John W. (1909 Apr 10)
Martin, Leslie H. (1899 Dec 21)
Martin, Thomas Staples (1899 Oct 28; 1900 Mar 9; 1908 Jun 19, Dec 3)
Mason, F.M. (1909 Nov 1)
Mason, George (1905 Apr 29; 1908 Jun 4)
Massie, C.G. (1905 Aug 3)
Massie, John H. (1909 Aug 10)
Matthews, J.C. (1905 Mar 16)
Matthews, Lee (1908 Dec 24)
Matthews, S. Wilkins (1909 Nov 8)
Matthews, William B. (1909 May 29, Dec 30)
Mayer, John F. (1900 Mar 8)
Maynard, H.L. (1908 Aug 28)
Mayo, P.H. (1908 Oct 21)
Mead, F.B. (1909 Jan 12)
Meade, R.H. (1910 Feb 9)
Meadors, D.T. (1905 Jul 15)
Meany, Edward P. (1899 Sept 26; 1900 Jan 24, Jan 30, Mar 27, Mar 31, Apr 5; 1902 Nov 3; 1907 Apr 3)
Meek, Samuel W. (1909 Jul 23)
Menefee, R.M. (1905 Jun 8)
Meredith, C.V. (1900 Mar 5)
Meredith, William (1905 Jun 29)
Meredith, Wyndham Robertson (1909 Nov 23)
Meriwether, H.S. Mrs. (1909 May 27)
Michie, E.M. (1905 Mar 27)
Midyette, D.R. (1905 Mar 6)
Miley, S.B. (1900 May 5)
Miller, Alexander (1899 Aug 23)
Miller, Howell M. (1905 Jun 29)
Miller, Polk (1905 Jan 31)
Miller, S.M. (1907 Apr 11)
Miller, T.A. (1908 Oct 23)
Miller, Thomas C. (1900 Jul 19, July 26)
Miller, W. Withers (1910 Apr 13)
Millhiser, Gustavus (1910 Apr 22)
Mills, J.T. (1905 Mar 15)
Mills, Mary and John (1909 Sept 13)
Mills, Spiller (1905 Jul 6)
Minor, J.T. (1905 Jul 6)
Mitchell, W.H. (1905 Jul 11)
Moffett, W.W. (1909 Jan 20)
Moncure, R.C.L. (1899 Aug 14, Aug 28; 1908 Jun 5)
Montague, A.P. (1907 Dec 13)
Montague, Andrew Jackson (1897 Aug 10, Oct 8 [2 letters], Nov 11; 1905 May 8; 1906 Feb 1)
Montague, Harriette Lee (1907 Apr 19)
Montgomery, Thomas L. (1908 Jul 8)
Moon, A.H. (1908 Nov 11)
Moon, J.W. (1905 Jun 24)
Moon, John Barclay (1908 May 20)
Moon, Lily B. (1900 Jul 26)
Moore, C. Lee (1898 Jan 20)
Moore, Edgar B. (1909 Apr 24, May 4, May 5, May 11)
Moore, Frank (1905 Apr 28)
Moore, Henry (1905 June 30)
Moore, J.B. (1900 Jan 18)
Moore, L. Bruce (1909 May 25)
Moorman, George (1900 Feb 7, Feb 22)
Moorman, William H. (1905 Jun 28)
Morehouse, H.L. [Henry Lyman?] (1900 Mar 26; 1909 Nov 16)
Morgan, O.B. (1905 Jul 7)
Morris, A.R. (1899 Oct 24)
Morris, George W. (1896 Dec 2)
Morris, M.O. (1900 Mar 16, Mar 26)
Morris, W.D. (1907 Jan 11)
Morton, J.E. (1909 May 21)
Morton, Lee W. (1908 Jun 2)
Morton, T.C. (1905 Mar 17)
Mosby-Coleman, Mrs. Stuart (1910 Apr 29, May 10)
Moss, Charles H. (1899 Nov 6)
Mulford, Frank W. (1897 Aug 26)
Mullen, J.M. (1910 Sept 2)
Mullen, W.H. (1909 May 26)
Mulligan, E.M. (1909 Aug 27)
Munford, Beverly Bland (1900 Feb 17; 1909 Mar 27)
Munford, Thomas Taylor (1910 Feb 24)
Munn, W.H. (1897 Oct 22)
Murphy, John (1908 Dec 14)
Murrell, George E. (1905 Jun 24)
Musgrave, R.N. (1905 Jun 30)
Myers, Albert Cook (1908 Jun 18, Nov 17)
Myers, Edmund T.D. (1899 Dec 26)
Myers, Lilburn T. (1900 Feb 15)
Myers, William M. (1908 Sept 8, 1910 Jan 27)
Neathery, R.W. (1899 Dec 16)
Neblett, J.T. (1908 Jun 6; 1909 Jan 3)
Nelms, Bernard (1908 Sept 9)
Nelms, W.J. (1899 Dec 9; 1900 Jan 9, Feb 3)
Nelms, George W. (1909 Jul 26)
Nelson, Frank (1899 Aug 8)
Newland, D. Elbert (1905 Jul 10)
Newport News Furniture Company (1909 Apr 30)
New York American (1909 Jun 16)
Nice, Albert L. (1899 Jul 29)
Nichols, W.E. (1909 Aug 23)
Nicholson, D.A. (1905 Jun 24)
Ninde, F.F. (1899 Oct 1)
Noell, R.J. (1905 May 3)
Nofringen, William A. (1905 Jul 7)
Nolting, Carl H. (1910 Sept 5)
Norfolk City Board School (1910 Feb 3)
Norrell, Charles (1900 Apr 20)
Norris, R.O. (1905 Jul 31)
Norwood, Mary L. (1909 Mar 6; n.y. May 6)
Nunn, Mrs. Evelyn (1905 Jul 3)
Nunn, W.C. (1909 May 21)
Oden, B.F. (1908 Nov 2)
O'Flaherty, D.C. (1899 Dec 29; 1900 Jun 20)
Old, C.L. (1909 Feb 1)
Otey, Peter Johnson (1899 Sept 28; 1900 Jul 26)
Owen, A.E. (1900 Feb 9)
Owen, Aubrey L. (1909 Jul 10)
Owen, Miss Jerrie R. (1909 Nov 24, Nov 30)
Owen, W. Russell (1899 Sept 16)
Owens, E.W. (1900 March 10)
P.F.L. (1899 Dec 27)
Pace, H.C. (1905 Jul 12)
Page, Rosewell (1910 Aug 31; n.d.)
Page, Thomas Nelson (1905 Jan 11)
Pankey, G.R. (1909 Oct 11)
Parater, F.J. (1905 Mar 23, Apr 1, May 25)
Parater, J.H. (1905 Apr 5, May 14, Jun 13; 1908 August 9; 1909 Apr 23; 1910 Apr 24, May 1, May 29)
Parker, B.S. (1909 April 15)
Parker, E.W. (1900 Mar 1)
Parker, H.J. (1909 Aug 23)
Parker, John D. (1910 Jan 10, Jan 15)
Parker, John M. (1909 Dec 17, Dec 20)
Parker, V.A. (1909 Sept 28)
Parks, R.S. (1910 Jan 8)
Parlin, Mrs Annie Levy (1909 Jun 25)
Parrish, Mrs. L.K. (1909 Apr 16)
Patterson, A.W. (1899 Dec 15)
Patteson, Camm (1905, Jun 30)
Payne, R.T. (1905 July 6)
Payne, W.L. (1905 Jul 14)
Payne, William G., Jr. (1909 Mar 24, Apr 2)
Pearcy (1900 Apr 2)
Pearson, Thomas J. (1909 Aug 5)
Pendleton, William (1906 May 19)
Pennington, R.B. (1905 May 1)
Perkins, T.B. (1905 Mar 24)
Perkins, W.W. (1905 Jul 8)
Philips, Mrs. H.C. (1909 Dec 27)
Philips, L.E. (1905 Jun 30)
Philips, Louis C. (1906 Oct 4)
Phippen, J.L. (1909 Nov 5)
Pickett, William P. (1907 Feb 19)
Pierce, A.N. (1908 Jun 4)
Pitt, R.H. (1909 Jun 3, Sept 16)
Pollard, Joseph L. (1905 Apr 3)
Pollard, Robert N. (1908 Nov 17)
Pope, Robert Anderson (1909 Jan 22, Jan 27)
Porterfield, G.T. (1901 Nov 7)
Potts, H. (1907 Mar 27)
Poulson, H.N. (1900 Jul 28)
Powell, A. Theodore (1905 Jun 29)
Powell, J.J.A. (1899 Sept 30)
Powell, R.S. (1907 Oct 17)
Power, W.H. (1910 Mar 3)
Powers, Hiram (1905 Jun 5)
Powers, Robert W. (1899 Sept 22; 1905 Apr 19)
Pratt, G. Julian (1908 Jan 14)
Prett, William A. (1908 Jun 2)
Price, B.A. (1905 Jul 14)
Priddy, A.S. (1899 Oct 3)
Prince, W.L. (1909 Sept 14)
Purcell, John B. (1899 Nov 21)
Pyle, Howard (1907 Mar 31)
Quarles, Edwin L. (1910 Feb 10)
Quillen, C.P. (1906 Mar 1)
Quillen, S.B. (1910 Aug 20)
Quisenberry, W.Y. (1899 Nov 27)
Ragland, John D. (1910 Apr 13)
Ramey, W.P. (1905 May 8)
Ramsdell, J.G. (1910 Jun 3, Jun 13)
Randolph, Janet H.W. (1900 May 21, Jul 15, Jul 23, n.d)
Ranson, Thomas D. (1905 Jun 13)
Raper, John C. (1905 Jun 30)
Raws, J.W. (1905 Jul 13)
Ray, George H. (1908 Jul 2; 1909 Apr 30, Jun 16)
Rector, J.T. (1910 Feb 26)
Rector, T.B. (1905 Jun 30)
Red Cross, (1905 Feb 6)
Reed, Harriett Vance (1900 Mar 27)
Reed, R.E. (1909 Jun 17, Aug 23)
Reed, Stuart F. (1909 Aug 6)
Rees, William A. (1910 Mar 12)
Reese, E.F. (1908 May 12)
Reeves, Jere (1909 Jan 13)
Reid, E.S. (1900 Jun 14; 1907 Sept 27)
Reigwin, H.A. (1909 May 30)
Reynolds, Cuyler (1908 Jan 20)
Reynolds, John O. (1900 Jul 28)
Rhea, William F. (1909 Jul 7)
Rice, A.P. (1899 Sept 4)
Rice, Asa S. (1905 Jul 15)
Rice, William S. (1909 Nov 26)
Richardson, C.B. (1909 Oct 23)
Richardson, John W. (1905 Apr 12)
Richart, O.P. (1909 May 15)
Richmond Chamber of Commerce (1910 Feb 2)
Richmond, W.A. (1905 Apr 29)
Rinne, Floyd (1909 Aug 13)
Rison, George Townes (1907 Oct 31; 1908 Jun 6; 1909 Dec 27)
Rittenour, F.H. (1900 Feb 13)
Ritter, L.M. (1899 Jul 27, Aug 7)
Rixey, Randolph P. (1905 Jun 29; 1910 Feb 16)
Rivard, James A. (1899 Sept 10)
Rixey and Hiden Attorneys at Law (1909 Sept 10)
Roberts, Floyd H. (1907 Oct 14)
Roberts, Sye F. (1905 Mar 26)
Robertson, A.T. (1910 Jun 14)
Robertson, Fred (1906 Jan 26)
Robertson, Thomas Brown (1900 Jun 30, Jul 7)
Robin, A.H. (1899 Sept 7)
Robinson, Bird M. 1899 Oct 31, Nov 16 (1900 Feb 9, Feb 21, Mar 3, Mar 13, Mar 31, Apr 2, Apr 5, May 7, May 22, Jul 18)
1908 Nov 25 (1909 Feb 4, Feb 17, Feb 25, Mar 4, Mar 16, Mar 20 [2 letters and telegram], Apr 6, Apr 7, Apr 9, Apr 28, May 27, May 29, Jun 2, Jun 14, Jun 16, Jun 23, Jun 29, Sept 18, Sept 21, Oct 7, Oct 18, Nov 3, Dec 21, Dec 27, Dec 31)
(1910 Jan 19, Feb 17, Feb 18, Feb 21, Feb 28, Mar 2)
Robinson, E.S. (1905 Jun 28)
Robinson, H.S. (1910 Jan 24)
Robinson, Mrs. J. Ludees (1910 Jan 8, Feb 2)
Robinson, W.B. (1909 Nov 12)
Rogers, George W. (1909 May 31)
Rogers, Maude H. (1905 Jun 30)
Rogers, W.S. (1905 Jun 1)
Robins, Sally Nelson (1906 Jan 6)
Rogers, Waller G. (1909 Feb 25)
Romeike, Albert (1906 Aug 8; 1909 Jun 15)
Ronbull, Th. R. (1910 Jun 11)
Rose, Edward S. (1900 Feb 26, Feb 28)
Rowe, George S. (1910 Feb 15)
Rowland, A.J. (1909 Nov 2)
Rucker, Mrs. B.H. (1910 Jun 25)
Rudd, C.H. (1910 Feb 15)
Rudd, W.T. (1905 Jul 17)
Rudd, W. F. (1899 Dec 12, Dec 16)
Ruffin, H.C. (1899 Sept 15)
Ruffin, T.C. (1905 Mar 10)
Ruge, John G. (1910 Jan 25)
Ryan, James A.P. (1905 Jul 12)
Ryan, Thomas Fortune (1907 Feb 26; 1908 Jan 26, Dec 5, Dec 8, Dec 9; 1909 Jan 16; 1910 Jan 17, Feb 14)
Ryland, Charles H. (1900 Feb 15, Jul 18; 1906 Apr 7; 1907 Jan 5; 1909 Jan 20, May 26; 1910 Jan 15, Jan 17, Jan 27)
Ryland, Walter H. (1908 Jun 1)
Sadler, W.H. (1901 Jan 21)
St. Clair, P.F. (1908 Jun 4)
Sale, W.W. (1905 Apr 29)
Sanders, G.B. (1905 Jul 6)
Sands, William H. (1908 Jul 16)
Saunders, Edward Watts (1910 Aug 28)
Saunders, John R. (1907 Oct 14)
Saville, Charles O. (1900 Feb 2)
Schenck, Frederick B. (1900 Apr 23)
Scherer, J.J., Jr. (1909 Jun 15)
Schmelz, George A. (1910 Feb 5)
Schmelz, Henry L. (1899 Nov 27, Dec 1, Dec 4; 1900 Feb 10, Mar 19, Jun 19)
Seay, B.W. (1909 Apr 2)
Seay, P. Pollard (1910 Jan 21)
Seayle, George A. (1905 Jul 6)
Sefton, Edwin (1908 May 22)
Settle, John C. (1900 Jul 31)
Seward, Annie Belle (1905 Jul 6)
Sexton, Robert H. (1910 Aug 9)
Sexton, V.L. (1908 Jun 16)
Shackelford, George Scott (1900 Mar 6; 1910 Feb 14, Feb 21)
Shanklin, S.J. (1905 Jun 29)
Shelton, Joseph M. (1900 Jan 8, Jan 15)
Shelton, P.F. (1905 Jun 30)
Shelton, T.H. (1909 Apr 19)
Shelton, W.H. (1910 Jan 24)
Shepherd, B. Morgan (1910 Mar 5)
Shepherd, C.N. (1909 Sept 7)
Shepherd, J.H. (1905 Jun 29)
Shepherd, H.D. (1905 Jul 6)
Shepperd, G.T. (1902 Apr 30; 1905 May 2, Dec 9; 1906 Jan 6 [2 letters]; 1907 May 6)
Shewmake, Oscar L. (1909 Jan 12)
Shumate, L.D. (1905 Jul 11)
Sievers, T. William (1909 Apr 6)
Silvers, William (1908 Mar 18)
Simmerman, S.S. (1910 Aug 10)
Sinclair, A.W. (1905 Jun 30)
Sinnott, J.J. (1900 Jan 23)
Sisters of the Visitation, Convent of Monte Maria (1909 Jun 4)
Skeen, A.A. (1899 Oct 26, Nov 4)
Sluss, J.H. (1909 May 21)
Smith, Augustine J. (1900 May 9)
Smith, B. Pressley (1909 Jun 29, Nov 3; 1910 Feb 10)
Smith, Charles A. (1905 Jul 1)
Smith, George S. (1905 Jul 15)
Smith, H.L. (1909 Jun 28)
Smith, Harrison B. (1909 Jan 18, Jan 21)
Smith, J.C. (1905 Jul 17)
Smith, J.F. (1905 Mar 23)
Smith, L.W. (1899 Aug 6)
Smith, L.M. (1909 Mar 13)
Smith, Mrs. Mary Blanton (1900 Mar 27)
Smith, Sydney (1910 Feb 1)
Smith, W.C. (1910 Mar 3)
Smith, W.D. (1899 Oct 30; 1910 Aug 15)
Smith, W.R.L. (1905 Mar 16; 1910 Feb 1)
Snead, George T. (1907 Oct 14)
Snead, J.P. (1910 Mar 2, Mar 11)
Snead, W. Frank (1905 Jun 29)
Snelling, Grenville Temple (1909 May 15, May 19, May 25; 1910 Feb 9)
Snodgrass, W.J. (1906 Oct 26 [2 letters] )
Snyder, W.A. (1909 Aug 3)
Solomon, Simon (1906 Jul 17)
Southern Commercial Congress (1910 Jan 20)
Southward, Mrs. J.T. (1909 Oct 21)
Spencer, D.W. (1905 Jun 29)
Spencer, H.B. (1909 Jan 11, Jan 25)
Spencer, Robert L. (1908 Jun 1)
Spessard, N.E. (1905 April 28, May 1, May 20)
Spindle, B.T. (1900 Mar 7)
Squires, Fred D.L. (1910 Sept 22)
Stafford, James R. (1905 Aug 7)
Staples, Abram P. (1899 Oct 31)
Staples, Ray F. (1899 Sept 8)
Start, A.H. (1899 Oct 27)
Steel, George B. (1909 May 15)
Stein, Sam (1905 Apr 1)
Stephens, Leroy (1909 Nov 3)
Stephenson, H.U. (1908 Jun 2)
Stern, Philip N. (1909 Jan 21)
Stevenson, George E.T. (1909 Apr 8)
Stevenson, Grace G. (1909 Aug 24)
Steward, Mrs. J. Calvin (1909 Mar 20)
Steward, Mrs. T.H. (1905 Jun 12)
Stifler, J.M. (1900 Apr 28)
Stike, J.W. (1909 Aug 19)
Stillwell, J.T. (1909 Jan 6, Jan 21, Feb 9)
Stoakley, William S. (1905 Jun 28)
Stokes, E.C. (1899 Sept 14)
Stone, Edward L. (1905 Jul 7)
Stone, John B. (1910 Jan 9)
Stoner, K.B. (1897 Nov 9)
Stoner, William J. (1905 Jun 30)
Stonesifer, J.G. (1899 Oct 11)
Strader, George L. (1900 Jul 6, Jul 10)
Stratton, J. Taylor (1903 Jan 2; 1909 Jan 22, Apr 20, Jul 13; 1910 Mar 11)
Stratton, T.J. (1907 Oct 12)
Street, J.M. (1910 Mar 12)
Strode, Aubrey Ellis (1908 Jun 1)
Strother, A.W. (1905 Mar 20)
Stuart, Henry Carter (1908 Jan 25)
Stubbs, James N. (1905 May 3)
Styll, R.T. (1900 May 5, Jun 29)
Sumpter E.E., 1909 Nov 26)
Sutherland, J. Leroy (1909 Nov 18)
Sutton, James J. (1909 Jun 8)
Swanson, Claude Augustus (1906 Jan 18, May 29, Oct 30, Dec 4, Apr 17, Apr 23; 1910 Sept 8, Sept 15)
Sweeney, George W. (1906 Aug 2)
Swoope, Mrs. M.E. (1909 Jun 9)
Sydnor R. Walter (1905 Mar 16, Jun 24)
Tabb, John R. (1896 Dec 17)
Tabb, Thomas (1899 Oct 27, Oct 31, Dec 7; 1900 Jun 19, Jun 29, Jul 7)
Taggart, Thomas (1907 Oct 29, Dec 21)
Talbott, A.G. (1906 Feb 4)
Talcott, T.M.R. (1905 Mar 16)
Tale, T.L. (n.d.)
Tanner, C.W. (1900 Jan 26, Feb 2)
Tapscott, A.D. (1905 Jul 15)
Tarpey, M.F. (1908 Jan 6)
Tatum, Mrs. W.H. (1905 Apr 8)
Tavenner, Clyde H. (1910 Mar 2)
Taylor, G.W. (1900 Jan 12)
Taylor, George Braxton (1910 Jan 26)
Taylor, John M. (1899 Nov 11; 1900 Jan 5)
Taylor, J.P. (1905 May 1)
Taylor, V.B. (1909 Mar 11, Mar 25)
Taylor, W.C. (1909 Oct 12)
Taylor, Washington (1897 Nov 3, Nov 8)
Tead, Edward S. (1909 Oct 30)
Teagle, C.S. (1910 Mar 10)
Teel, J.F. (1909 Sept 7)
Tewksbury, Lewis G. & Company (1899 Dec 29)
Thomas, Alfred P. (1900 May 12)
Thomas, James (1905 Apr 24)
Thomas, John (1899 Nov 9)
Thomas, R.S. (1897 Aug 17, Dec 3; 1900 Jan 16)
Thomas, S. S. (1896 Dec 24)
Thompson, J. Taylor (1910 Jan 24)
Thornhill, E.L. (1909 Nov 16)
Thornhill, L.R. (1909 Sept 7)
Thraves, John T. (1905 Jun 30)
Thrift, J.E. (1907 Oct 15)
Tiffany, W.N. (1900 May 25)
Tiffany & Company (1908 Sept 29, Oct 7, Oct 26)
Tilson, William Frances (1905 Apr 8)
Tinsley, H.L. (1897 Dec 9, Dec 26, n.d. [2 letters])
Tirus, L.A. (1905 Mar 25)
Tompkins, Bessie McCaw (n.y. Dec 11)
Tompkins, R.N. (1905 Apr 4)
Travers, E. Mc. C. (1909 Mar 24)
Trehy, James V. (1905 Jul 18)
Trimble, Henry M. (1900 Mar 21)
Trimble, Richard (1900 Jan 9)
Truit, Coland (1909 Dec 23)
Tuck, Richard F. (1905 Jul 13)
Tucker, Henry St. George (1905 Feb 18, Mar 6, Mar 9;1906 Apr 17, Dec 21; 1907 Jan 5)
Tucker, J.R. (1909 Jan 4)
Turnbull, Robert (1900 Mar 10; 1910 Feb 5, n.d.)
Turner, Edna (1907 Mar 11)
Turnstall, W.P. (1905 Mar 25)
Turpin, John B. (1905 Jul 7)
Twyman, J.A. (1899 Dec 4)
Tyler, Mrs. Carrie (1909 Oct 23)
Tyler, D.G. (1910 Sept 20)
Tyler, Ielene (1900 Feb 7)
Tyler, James Hoge (1897 Aug 7, Sept 16, Nov 5; 1909 Oct 25)
Umstadter, M. (1908 Jan 28)
Underwood, John C. (1900 Jan 1, Feb 24, Apr 17[2 letters], May 14, Jun 23, Jul 2 [3 letters], Jul 6, Jul 26, Jul [?], n.d.)
Underwood, W.W. (1899 Dec 29)
Valentine, Henry Lee (1908 Sept 28; 1910 Jan 10)
Vanhoy, Mrs. N.H. (1910 Jan 31)
Van Buskirk, R.N. (1910 Jan 8, Jan 14)
Vandiver, Murray (1909 Oct 19)
Vaughn, J.L. (1905 Jul 9)
Venable, William H. (1910 Sept 17, Sept 23)
Victoria, S.W. (1907 Aug 10)
Virginia State Democratic Committee (1901 Dec 2)
Vorster, B.S. (1905 Apr 12)
Waddill, W.W. (1900 Mar 2)
Wagner, P (1908 Apr 13, Sept 1, Sept 9)
Walker, C. Irvine (1910 Mar 23)
Walker, T.A. (1909 Jul)
Wallace, Charles M. Jr. (1897 Nov 5)
Wallace, G.M. (1907 Sept 10)
Wallach, C. (1897 Nov 1)
Waller, N.S. (1908 Apr 29)
Wall Street Information Bureau (1908 Sept 2, Sept 11)
Ward, Robert M. (1907 Oct 21; 1909 Dec 29)
Waring, John L. (1900 Feb 15)
Warren, P.T. (1899 Aug 9)
Washington Post (1909 Aug 3)
Watkins, A.D. (1908 May 13)
Watkins, G.T. (1899 Aug 4, Nov 21)
Watson, John L. (1910 Sept 21)
Watson, P.P. (1897 Nov 3)
Watts, [Leigh](1897 Oct 28)
Webb, Charles S. (1905 Jul 6)
Wedderburn, Alex J. (1909 Mar 16)
Wellford, R. Carter (1898 Sept 12)
Wells, J.M. (1905 Jul 18)
West, George B. (1900 Jul 6)
West, Junius Edgar (1909 Nov 23, Dec 29; 1910 Aug 31)
Wev, Mrs. Nellie (1909 Nov 29)
Wharton, Henry M. (1900 Apr 20, Apr 26)
Wheatley, George W. & Company (1908 Apr 24)
Wheeler, William M. (1905 Jun 30)
Whiddit, William Wall (1909 Jul 12)
White, Bessie Samuel (1905 Mar 17)
White, C.W. (1897 Nov 1)
White, Joel W. (1907 Dec 30)
White, John B. (1909 Nov 1)
White, John H. (1899 Aug 21)
White, John M. (1910 Aug 30)
White, M.H. (1899 Aug 9)
White, Peter J. (1909 Apr 20, Jul 13)
White, Robert 1898 Dec 21 (1900 May 8, Jun 11, Jun 14, Jun 19, Jun 21, Jun 24, Jun 26, Jul 6 [2 letters])
1905 Apr 24, Apr 29, May 6, May 11 (1908 Dec 28; 1909 Jan 14, Jun 2, Jun 15, Aug 14, Sept 26, Sept 28, Nov 4, Nov 20)
White, W.F. (1909 Feb 8)
White, William Henry (1909 Feb 1, Nov 5, Nov 16; 1910 Feb 26, Jun 22)
White, William L. (1909 Dec 22)
Whitecarver, W.B. (1905 Jul 15)
Whitehead, Irving P. (1910 Jan 24)
Whitehead, R.B. (1907 Mar 4 [2 letters])
Wiatt, A.T. (1905 Jun 29)
Wiatt, William E. (1907 Aug 20; 1909 May 21, Jun 30, Aug 22, Oct 8, Nov 20)
Wickham, T. Ashby (1910 Aug 11)
Wilkinson, J. Samuel (1904 Mar 31)
Wilkinson, L.A. (1909 Feb 12)
Wilkinson, T.E. (1905 Jun 19)
Willard, Joseph E. (1900 July 9; 1905 Apr 28)
Willcox, J. Westmore (1909 Mar 5)
William, Ennion Gifford (1909 Sept 3)
Williams, Thomas C. Jr. (1900 Jul 6)
Williams, Thomas N. (1900 Jul 12; 1905 Apr 28)
Williams, W. Jones (1905 Jul 18)
Williamson, H.J. (1909 Sept 2)
Willingham, R.J. (1900 Mar 16)
Willis, C.B. (1910 Aug 25)
Willis, M.L. (1908 Jul 13)
Wilson, George A. (1905 Jul 15)
Wilson, Harry L. (1909 Feb 27)
Wilson, R.O. (1906 Apr 10)
Wilson, Woodrow (1910 Sept 21)
Wiltshire, J.H. (1905 Jul 18)
Wily, George A. (1905 Jul 14)
Wimbish, William A. (1910 Feb 2)
Winfrey, E.W. (1909 Jun 16; 1910 Feb 14)
Winfrey, George H. (1905 Mar 15; 1907 Jun 10)
Wingfield, John Richard (1910 Feb 21)
Winn, Mrs. Kate S. (1905 May 17)
Winston, James Blair (1899 Aug 16, Sept 21; 1901 Dec 11)
Withers, Robert W. (1910 Mar 26)
Withington, Lothrop (1906 Jun 5, Jun 26, Jul 6; 1907 Feb 6, Mar 9, Mar 12, Apr 18, Apr 19, Apr 30)
Wittingham, R.J. (1899 Aug 10)
Wolfe, D.C. (1905 Jun 29)
Wolfe, L.C. (1899 Aug 21)
Wood, Joseph (1905 Jul 17)
Woodard, A.G. (1899 Nov 28)
Woodfin, A.B. (1906 Nov 20)
Woodfin, Paul Beverly (1909 Jan 19 [2 letters])
Woodruff, Clinton Rogers (1909 Sept 6)
Woods, James P. (1907 Oct 15)
Woodson, Urey (1907 Jan 13)
Woodward, J.B. (1905 Mar 24)
Woodward, W.J. (1905 Jul 14)
Woody, C.C. (Miss)
(1909 Jan 15)
Wool, T.J. (1907 Sept 12)
Word, L.E. (1908 Jun 1)
Worrell, C.C. (1906 Oct 23)
Wortham, T.M. (1910 Feb 16)
Wright, M.G. (1905 Mar 20, May 2)
Wyche, B.W. (1905 Jun 30)
Yarbrough, G.W. (1905 Apr 1)
Yellott, R.E.L. (1899 Nov 2)
Yoakum, Benjamin Franklin (1910 Jan 19)
Young Men's Christian Association. (1902 Jul 1)
Ziou, George W. (1905 Jul 5)
LETTERS FROM JAMES TAYLOR ELLYSON INCLUDE:
Alderman, Edwin A. (1910 Jan 6)
Allen, G.T. (1910 Jan 10)
Amos, Leonard (1909 Sept 17)
Asher, M.T. (1909 Nov 2)
Barrett, A.S. (1905 Jun 24)
Benton, W.C. (1909 Nov 30)
Board of Directors of the Chamber of Commerce of Birmingham, Alabama (1909 Dec 22)
Boatwright, F.W. (1909 Oct 16, Oct 25)
Bolling, Stith (1909 Aug 31)
Bowman, A.M. (1909 Sept 10)
Buchanan, B.F. (1909 Jan 6)
Button, Joseph (1909 Dec 28)
Cameron, William E. (1909 Oct 25)
Carson, A.R. (1899 Oct 30)
Caton, James R. (1908 Apr 30)
Chalkley, Mrs. W.F. (1909 Oct 1)
Christian, Walter (1909 Nov 4)